

# LEADERSHIP SKILLS

Organized planner
Creative problem-solver
Passionate listener
Empatic motivator
Engaging speaker
Resilient
Initiative taker
Creative spirit
Reliable and professional
Time management
Team player
Fast learner
Motivated

# **REMOTE TOOLS**

- Slack
- Google Drive
- Zoom
- Trello
- Coggle
- Togal
- Zendesk
- Connecteam
- VSCode
- Sandbox
- Github
- Netlify

# MARIËTTE EVERITZ

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a motivated, passionate Customer Server with over 5 years of experience in Customer Support in international, non-profit and profit, educational and creative industries. Interested in joining multicultural organizations where I can apply my knowledge and skills for continuous improvement and share the same values.

#### RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

MARKETING - CONTENT SITE MANAGER

Paynovate | August 2021 - Now

- Improving and investigating customer contentment by taking note and necessary action in customer experiences.
- Providing documentation/strategies for colleagues to solve problems of customers and create positive outcome.

# **OPERATIONS**

Paynovate | August 2020 - Now

- Thoroughly check contracts: company validities, shareholders, given information and perform background checks.
- Migration validation
- Providing documentation and coach/training of (new) colleagues to create better strategies and service.

#### FIRST LINER SUPPORT AGENT

Loyaltek | February 2020 - Now

- Provide problemsolving solutions & support to hosts via e-mail and phone.
- Make and solve tickets for the second liners.
- Help improve the remote department of the company (improve communication, documents, employee satisfaction.

Evaluate customer, colleague and own experiences to create better strategies and service.

#### TELEMARKETING CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT

Sitel Barcelona - Oui.sncf | June 2019 - December 2019

- Provide world class customer service and support via e-mail, phone, chat and social media
- Make tickets for the claim department of refunds and complaints of customers
- Using exceptional people skills to get out in front of potential problems and proactively help customers

Evaluate customer and own experiences to create better upscaled strategies and service.

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT & SALES

Cygnific - KLM & De persgroep - Indebuurt | Nov 2018 - Juni 2019

- Deliver world class customer service and support
- Create tickets for customer claims, complaints and feedback/suggestions
- Evaluate and identify opportunities for process improvement
- Identify sales opportunities and create sale leads
- Pass on creative advise and tips on increasing revenue to B2B customers



# LANGUAGES

• Dutch: Native

• English: Near Native

• Papiamento: Near Native

• Spanish: Intermediate

# MARIËTTE EVERITZ

# EXPERIENCES

#### SALES EXECUTIVE

De persgroep - Indebuurt | Feb 2019 - Juni 2019

- Deliver world class customer service and support
- Evaluate and identify opportunities for process improvement
- Identify sales opportunities and create sale leads
- Pass on creative advise and tips on increasing revenue to B2B customers Help companies increase in revenues and build customer loyalty.

#### OPERATION MANAGEMENT/MARKET RESEARCH

EF Education First (Corporate)| March 2018 - JuLy 2018 (Graduate/Thesis Intership)

- Give remote presentations and demonstrations to new users..
- Evaluate experiences and communications with users by creating and sending out surveys, analyze the data and make presentations for the empleyrs
- Analyse and create monthly reports of the progress of employees for the companies.
- Support the sales team by searching for new sale leads
- Complete administrative tasks in Salesforce for the sales team.

Creating a ready to implement Marketing Strategic plan on how to position a new B2B product in the Dutch market.

#### SALES AND RECRUITER/BUSINESS RESEARCH

Mr. Search/LER | Sept 2016 - Feb 2017 (Intership)

- Use the selection and improvement process and evluate the current process.
- Analyse and evaluate the desires and needs within the company (goals and mission)
- Create new strategies, implement and evaluate for the Strategy plan.
- Search for candidates per vacancy, contact them (interview the candidates and scan the resumes)
- Introduce the candidates to the companies and evaluate candidates with the company. Evaluate the internal business process and create a ready to use Process Strategy plan to improve the selection and recruitment process.

#### AMBASSADOR, MENTOR & CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT

University of Applied Sciences | April 2015 - June 2018

- Provide the best customer service and support for (future) students, parents and teachers face-to-face and via e-mail.
- Give presentations and coaching at schools
- Evaluate experiences of and communications with future applicants by creating ideas for process improvement
- Help resolve any issue and/or doubts
- Planning activities for my colleagues for teambuilding and to pass on motivation and creativity in giving service.

Increased student application with 175% and decreased the number of dropouts/education change with 160%



### WHO AM I

I am a strong believer in passing on knowledge, creativity and motivation. On a daily basis, I am making my surrounding crazy with being very positive and coming up with ideas how they can accomplish their dreams and desires.

My motto: 'Dare to dream, don't settle for less.'

I am always learning and like to identify trends. One of my missions is to travel around the world (or atleast 3/4 of it;)) and spread my positive motivation and believes that everyone can accomplish their dream. I like to be challenged, enjoy getting out of my comfy zone and learn/experience new things.

# **HOW TO CONTACT ME**

Email: mariette.everitz@outlook.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/marietteeveritz

Skype: mariette\_ve or mariette.everitz@outlook.com

# MARIËTTE EVERITZ

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF ARTS: BUSINESS STUDIES, MAJOR IN ENTREPRENEURSHIP

University of Aplied Sciences Inholland | 2014 - 2018

MASTOR OF SCIENCE: MAJOR IN EDUCATION, TUTORING AND COACHING

IPA Aruba | 2007 - 2011

COLLEGE IN ECONOMICS: MAJOR IN FINANCE, ECONOMICS

EPI Economia Aruba | 2003 - 2007

## COURSES

CERTIFIED ELITE PERFOMANCE COACHING (CERTIFICATE) (2022) SHECODES: WEB DEVELOPMENT (BASIC, PLUS REACT, RESPONSIVE (SEO)) (2021) CODE INSTITUTE 5-DAY CODING CHALLENGE (CERTIFICATE) (2021)

SPANISH (2007 / 2020 - ONGOING)
TRADING BY CONFLUENCE KINGS (2020)

# **MAIN INTERESTS**

Volunteerwork: create activities/show and teach creative art classes with and for kids, youth & young adults

Sports: Dance, Diving, Fitness, Kickboxing, Hiking, Soccer Traveling: exploring & learning about different cultures

Web development: coding (websites/apps)

Coaching: Motivation in Life